http://www.bostoncasting.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Rhode Island Casting, Inc.CONTACT US BY EMAILCOVID-19 UPDATESFeature FilmsIndependent FilmsTelevisionCommercialsClientsBoston Acting ClassesAbout Us & AwardsStaffAgencyPro Talent DatabaseExtrasVideo LibraryFAQDirectionsTalent LoginTalent ApplicationClient LoginClient ApplicationPrivacy PolicyChild Labor FormsSelf-Tape InstructionsWhat's New
Privacy Policy
Boston Casting respects your privacy. We collect personally identifying information from you only when you specifically provide it. This policy describes what information we collect and how we treat it.
Information We Collect
Boston Casting may collect information from you when you enter it on our website or provide it to us through other forms of contact. We gather information you may provide in the context of mailing in a resume or headshot, registering for newsletters or online updates, filling out an information form, or contacting us with a query. The information we collect may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, interests, or other data or images you provide. Your participation in these activities is entirely voluntary; if you do not wish to provide your information, you may of course visit our website anonymously and refrain from participating in activities that request personal information.
How We Use the Information
Boston Casting’s goal in collecting your personal data is to provide you with potential employment opportunities. We use the information you provide us to respond to your requests, provide you information and offer you educational and employment opportunities. We may share your information with companies that contract us for services (such as, but not limited to, advertising agencies, photographers, corporate clients, production companies). We may also share your information with business partners who can provide you with information or offers that may interest you as well as unions who require such information to process employment or potential employment. Examples of our business partners include Digital Casting and AgencyPro Software, the company that provides Boston Casting with database management services. You may receive information or offers from companies such as these to participate in other services they provide. For more information about AgencyPro Software and its privacy policy, please visit www.agencyprotalent.com. Your decision to accept or decline such offers from any of our affiliates or business partners does not negatively affect your status at Boston Casting. We never expect or accept money, directly or indirectly, from talent in exchange for placement.
In the unlikely event that Boston Casting or substantially all of its assets are acquired by another company, customer information is likely to be among the assets transferred. Finally, we may release customer information when we believe it is necessary to comply with laws or court orders, to enforce our policies or contracts, or to protect users of our site from fraudulent or abusive use.
Maintaining the Confidentiality and Security of Your Information
We retain records relating to our services that we provide so that we are better able to assist you with your professional needs. In order to guard your non-public personal information, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with our professional standards.
Your Consent
By submitting personal information to Boston Casting, you consent to the collection and use of that information in the manner described in this policy. Boston Casting reserves the right to change its policy in this regard at any time in the future. In the event that we do change our policy, we will notify you of those changes promptly, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
If you have any questions, or if you would like to make corrections to your personal information, please contact Boston Casting. Your privacy concerns are important to us.
